awakeningwiththemasters.com 2017-12-27

# Empowered You Media - Privacy

**EMPOWERED YOU MEDIA** is committed to respecting your privacy. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and considered a part of, the Terms of Access and Use Agreement and Purchase Agreement/Terms of Sale policies. By accessing our websites, you explicitly consent to this Privacy Policy.

#### Section 1: User Consent 

By submitting or making available personal data through our websites or purchase of goods or services from us, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your personal data may be processed in the United States or in other countries where laws regarding the processing of personal data may be less stringent than the laws in the United States. 

#### Section 2: Types of Personal Data Collected

When you purchase a Product from **EMPOWERED YOU MEDIA** , personal data may be collected from you, such as first and last name, email and mailing addresses, telephone number, professional title, company name, and password, when you purchase Products, register to receive information, or access our website(s) for other purposes. In addition, we (or our third-party credit card of payment processor on our behalf) will collect personal data including your credit card number or account information when you purchase products or services on our websites. Credit card information is kept at the highest level of security and is never divulged to anyone except the service provider or for the purpose of communication with you.

If you participate in any of our surveys, we may collect additional information regarding your preferences or comments. We also retain information from you regarding any correspondence, forum postings, or other feedback you provide to us. Any comments provided to us about our Products or services may be used as testimonials to others.

To make our websites, Products, and related services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third-party service provider) collects personal data from you, such as browser type, operating system, IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain names, and/or date and time stamp for your visit. We may also use Cookies and navigational data, such as URLs (Uniform Resource Locators) to gather information regarding the date/time of your visit and the information for which you searched and viewed. 

#### Section 3: Use/Disclosure of Personal Data

**Live Big Media’s policy is that it will not sell, lease, or rent your personal data to others without your express consent.**   
In general, your personal data is used by us to respond to your requests or to aid us in serving you better. Your personal data may be used to facilitate the creation of and secure your account on our network; identify you as a user in our system; provide improved administration of our website, Products, and services; improve the quality of experience when you interact with our websites; send you administrative email notifications; send you promotional communications and special offers; make telephone calls to you from time to time; or to solicit your feedback.

We may create data records from your personal data that excludes information that makes the data not personally identifiable to you - we call this Anonymous Data. We use this Anonymous Data to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Products and service, and improve navigation of our websites. We reserve the right to use Anonymous Data for other purposes and to disclose this data to third parties. 

We may share your personal data with third parties to provide technical support or to provide specific services, such as hosting, payment processing of purchases, agents, contractors, or business partners for the purpose of performing services for Live Big Media or its affiliated companies. 

Please be aware that our advertisers or web site that may have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those web sites linked to our web site, either through advertisement or other hyperlinks, are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

#### Section 4: Security of Personal Data

Empowered You Media is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Data. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We also require you to enter a password to access your account information. Please do not share your password with others. Despite the measure we take, security risks and the potential for a security breach still exist. 

#### Section 5: Third Party Sites

Third-party Internet sites and services accessible through our web site have separate privacy and data collection policies, independent of us. Empowered You Media has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information through the transmission process and you do so at your own risk.

#### Section 6: Opt Out Policy/Request to Delete Account Information

We collect information about your activities on certain websites to send you targeted ads, communications, and promotional materials. When you receive ads, promotions or other communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the instructions included at the bottom of that communication.

You may request deletion of your account information by use, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your request to delete your account information only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete account information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. To submit your request to delete your account information, please email emailsupport {@} empoweredyoumedia .com. 

#### Section 7: Legal Notice

Any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use and Access <http://www.empoweredyoumedia.com/terms.html>, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of Iowa. If you have any concerns about your privacy in connection with this policy, please send us an email at Email and we will attempt to resolve your concern. We reserve the right to revise our Privacy Policy at any time and we encourage you to check our web site frequently to note any changes. 

#### Section 8: Company Contact Information

Empowered You Media   
110 N. IH-35 Suite 315-135   
Round Rock, TX 78681   
support [@] empoweredyoumedia .com
